sitepopula.com 2013-11-28

# SitePopula.com Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by SitePopula.com and how it is used.

## Log Files

Like many other Websites, SitePopula.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information.

IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

SitePopula.com does use cookies to store information about visitor’s preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitor’s browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on SitePopula.com. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to SitePopula.com and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL <http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/privacy-policy.html>

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google AdSense.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on SitePopula.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs.

Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

SitePopula.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

## Visitor Name and Email address

We are not requiring visitor to provide any personal information such as name and Email address to us for visiting SitePopula.com

Visitors may provide their first name and email address to SitePopula.com. And the reason we collect the first name is we want to make more friendly when sending or replying email to the user.

When they ask questions or provide comments to us. We use this information for replying back the question and comment that have been send to us.

## The Change of This Privacy Policy

Since we continued improvement SitePopula.com and quality and adding new features, we may need to make some change or add some new policy when we necessary. We may not inform to the visitor about change; but we may publish about the change on a specific date later.
